title	rating	ratingLevel	ratingDescription	release year	user rating score	user rating size
White Chicks	PG-13	"crude and sexual humor, language and some drug content"	80	2004	82	80
Lucky Number Slevin	R	"strong violence, sexual content and adult language"	100	2006	NA	82
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
How I Met Your Mother	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	94	80
Supernatural	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Breaking Bad	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	97	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
The Walking Dead	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	98	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
Once Upon a Time	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	98	80
Sherlock	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Death Note	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2006	77	80
Naruto	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2008	88	80
The Hunter	R	language and brief violence	100	2011	NA	82
Lottie Dottie Chicken	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2009	NA	82
Arrow	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	96	80
Black Mirror	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	80	80
The Originals	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
The 100	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	97	80
Masha and the Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	81	80
"ÌÒ Pai, ÌÒ - Look at This"	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2007	NA	82
Nymphomaniac: Volume 1	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2013	NA	82
Hunter X Hunter (2011)	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2013	57	80
Marvel's Luke Cage	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	95	80
Marvel's Iron Fist	TV-MA		110	2017	98	80
Narcos	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	94	80
The Flash	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	98	80
The Seven Deadly Sins	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Scream	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Do-Over	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	84	80
OperaÌ¤Ìµes Especiais	TV-MA		110	2015	NA	82
3%	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Trollhunters	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	83	80
Fearless	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Hyena Road	R	"bloody war violence, language throughout and some sexual material"	100	2015	NA	82
Santa Clarita Diet	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	82	80
"Sex, Love and Therapy"	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2014	NA	82
White Girl	UR	"This movie has not been rated. Intended for adults only and may contain sex, violence, drugs, language or other adult themes."	124	2016	NA	82
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
City of God: 10 Years Later	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	NA	82
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Sand Castle	TV-MA		110	2017	89	80
Salvador Martinha - Tip of the Tongue	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Sandy Wexler	TV-14		90	2017	92	80
O Amor no DivÌ£	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Stronger Than the World	NR		124	2016	NA	82
Back and Forth	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	NA	82
Happily Married	TV-14		90	2015	NA	82
Pandora	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Lucky Number Slevin	R	"strong violence, sexual content and adult language"	100	2006	NA	82
The Office (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	97	80
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
90210	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	62	80
Gossip Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	96	80
How I Met Your Mother	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	94	80
Supernatural	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Breaking Bad	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	97	80
Parks and Recreation	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	94	80
Glee	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	92	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
Family Guy	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	98	80
Criminal Minds	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Friends	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2003	98	80
The Secret Life of the American Teenager	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	81	80
One Tree Hill	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	90	80
The Walking Dead	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	98	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
American Horror Story	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	90	80
Orange Is the New Black	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	98	80
Inside Russia's Toughest Prison	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	NA	82
Black Mirror	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	80	80
Bates Motel	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	83	80
The 100	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	97	80
Marvel's Iron Fist	TV-MA		110	2017	98	80
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
How to Get Away with Murder	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
The Get Down	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	80	80
Love	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
The Flash	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	98	80
The OA	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Stranger Things	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	90	80
Ingobernable	TV-MA		110	2017	96	80
Zootopia	PG	"some thematic elements, rude humor and action"	60	2016	97	80
Meet the Blacks	R	"pervasive language, some sexual material, violence and drug use"	100	2016	79	80
Finding Dory	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2016	98	80
Santa Clarita Diet	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	82	80
Sausage Party	R	"strong crude sexual content, pervasive language, and drug use"	100	2016	91	80
Pete's Dragon	PG	"for action, peril and brief language"	60	2016	93	80
Kevin Hart: What Now?	R	"some sexual material, and language throughout"	100	2016	97	80
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
The Discovery	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Sand Castle	TV-MA		110	2017	89	80
Sandy Wexler	TV-14		90	2017	92	80
Chewing Gum	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	93	80
Cheer Squad	TV-PG		70	2016	61	80
Only for One Night	TV-MA		110	2016	78	80
The Life Aquatic with Steve Zissou	R	"language, some drug use, violence and partial nudity"	100	2004	NA	82
Lucky Number Slevin	R	"strong violence, sexual content and adult language"	100	2006	NA	82
The L Word	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2009	NA	82
The Office (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	97	80
30 Rock	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	66	80
Mad Men	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	75	80
It's Always Sunny in Philadelphia	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	91	80
Californication	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2014	63	80
Parks and Recreation	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	94	80
Friends	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2003	98	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
Portlandia	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	62	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Don't Trust the B---- in Apartment 23	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	NA	82
Friends with Benefits	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	NA	82
The Client List	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	92	80
Halt and Catch Fire	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
5 to 7	R	some sexual material	100	2014	NA	82
Marvel's Iron Fist	TV-MA		110	2017	98	80
Chef's Table	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Documentary Now!	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
Better Call Saul	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	95	80
The Get Down	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	80	80
Schitt's Creek	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
Lovesick	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Flaked	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Master of None	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	NA	82
Chelsea	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Abstract: The Art of Design	TV-14		90	2017	NA	82
Cooper Barrett's Guide to Surviving Life	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Great British Baking Show	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	94	80
Life in Pieces	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	68	80
Crazy Ex-Girlfriend	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	NA	82
Easy	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Santa Clarita Diet	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	82	80
No Tomorrow	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Minimalism: A Documentary About the Important Things	TV-PG		70	2016	NA	82
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
Hot Girls Wanted: Turned On	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
The Discovery	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Sandy Wexler	TV-14		90	2017	92	80
Chewing Gum	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	93	80
Win It All	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
MerlÌ?	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	NA	82
Amy Schumer: The Leather Special	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Louis C.K. 2017	TV-MA		110	2017	71	80
Dave Chappelle	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	94	80
Almost Adults	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	NA	82
The Brothers	R	strong sexual content and language	100	2001	NA	82
Skins	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	NA	82
The Cleveland Show	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	88	80
Absolutely Fabulous	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	59	80
Don't Trust the B---- in Apartment 23	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	NA	82
Raising Hope	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	73	80
Come Fly With Me	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2010	NA	82
Orange Is the New Black	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	98	80
Brickleberry	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2014	63	80
Bates Motel	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	83	80
BoJack Horseman	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Being Mary Jane: The Series	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Documentary Now!	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Get Down	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	80	80
Love	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Bordertown	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	86	80
Jane The Virgin	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Schitt's Creek	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
Dope	R	"language, drug content, sexuality/nudity, and some violence-all involving teens"	100	2015	79	80
Lovesick	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
The Carmichael Show	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	69	80
Cooper Barrett's Guide to Surviving Life	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Great British Baking Show	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	94	80
November Rule	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	NA	82
Life in Pieces	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	68	80
Crazy Ex-Girlfriend	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	NA	82
Easy	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Haters Back Off	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	58	80
Kubo and the Two Strings	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, action and peril"	60	2016	96	80
Skins	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
A Weekend with the Family	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Crazyhead	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Queen of Katwe	PG	"thematic elements, an accident scene and some suggestive material"	60	2016	NA	81
Little Boxes	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	61	80
Deidra & Laney Rob a Train	TV-14		90	2017	NA	82
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
Hot Girls Wanted: Turned On	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Hurricane Bianca	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Honeytrap	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2014	NA	82
Greenleaf	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	62	80
Lazy Eye	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Like Cotton Twines	NR		124	2016	NA	82
The Wedding Party	TV-14		90	2016	NA	82
Dave Chappelle	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	94	80
Only for One Night	TV-MA		110	2016	78	80
Boy Bye	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Almost Adults	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	NA	82
Nancy Drew	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2007	NA	82
30 Rock	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	66	80
Nurse Jackie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	82	80
Parks and Recreation	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	94	80
Drop Dead Diva	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	NA	82
Gilmore Girls	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2006	91	80
Parenthood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	79	80
Life Unexpected	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2010	55	80
Portlandia	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	62	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Don't Trust the B---- in Apartment 23	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	NA	82
Raising Hope	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	73	80
Being Human (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	58	80
Friends with Benefits	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	NA	82
The Carrie Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	NA	82
Baby Daddy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	80	80
Halt and Catch Fire	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Angriest Man in Brooklyn	R	Restricted. May be inappropriate for children 17 and under.	100	2014	NA	82
5 to 7	R	some sexual material	100	2014	NA	82
Chef's Table	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
Unbreakable Kimmy Schmidt	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Get Down	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	80	80
Sense8	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	81	80
Love	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Bordertown	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	86	80
Girlfriends' Guide to Divorce	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	63	80
Schitt's Creek	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
The Carmichael Show	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	69	80
Chelsea	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	NA	82
Abstract: The Art of Design	TV-14		90	2017	NA	82
Cooper Barrett's Guide to Surviving Life	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
The Great British Baking Show	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	94	80
Life in Pieces	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	68	80
Crazy Ex-Girlfriend	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	NA	82
Fried	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	NA	82
The Great Gilly Hopkins	PG	for thematic material and language	60	2016	69	80
The Magicians	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	89	80
One Day at a Time	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2017	NA	82
No Tomorrow	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Hot Girls Wanted: Turned On	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Better Off Single	TV-MA		110	2016	NA	82
Sandy Wexler	TV-14		90	2017	92	80
Chewing Gum	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	93	80
The Matchbreaker	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2016	79	80
Tramps	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Slam	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Cheer Squad	TV-PG		70	2016	61	80
Almost Adults	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	NA	82
The Waterboy	PG-13	language and some crude sexual humor	80	1998	82	80
10 Things I Hate About You	PG-13	"adult content, adult language and mild violence"	80	1999	68	80
Grease	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1978	86	80
How to Lose a Guy in 10 Days	PG-13	some sex-related material	80	2003	56	80
The Benchwarmers	PG-13	"crude and suggestive humor, and for language"	80	2006	77	80
Step Up	PG-13	"thematic elements, brief violence and innuendo"	80	2006	64	80
High School Musical 2	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2007	58	80
Twilight	PG-13	some violence and one sexual scene	80	2008	89	80
Coraline	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, some language and suggestive humor"	60	2009	95	80
Hannah Montana: The Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	56	80
The Office (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	97	80
Friday Night Lights	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2010	81	80
StarStruck	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	NA	82
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
90210	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	62	80
Gossip Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	96	80
How I Met Your Mother	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	94	80
Glee	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	92	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
Family Guy	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	98	80
Criminal Minds	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Friends	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2003	98	80
Mean Girls 2	PG-13	"For some rude and suggestive material, and for language."	80	2011	NA	82
The Secret Life of the American Teenager	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	81	80
That '70s Show	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2005	89	80
Gilmore Girls	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2006	91	80
Parenthood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	79	80
Heartland	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	85	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
Switched at Birth	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	83	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Hart of Dixie	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	81	80
The Client List	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	92	80
The Carrie Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	NA	82
Safe Haven	PG-13	"thematic material involving threatening behavior, and for violence and sexuality"	80	2013	62	80
Baby Daddy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	80	80
The Night Shift	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	93	80
Reign	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	79	80
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
How to Get Away with Murder	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Fuller House	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	90	80
Finding Dory	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2016	98	80
Gilmore Girls: A Year in the Life	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	77	80
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Gabriel lglesias: I‰Ûªm Sorry For What I Said When I Was Hungry	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	84	80
Amy Schumer: The Leather Special	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Cheer Squad	TV-PG		70	2016	61	80
Dave Chappelle	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	94	80
The Waterboy	PG-13	language and some crude sexual humor	80	1998	82	80
Grease	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1978	86	80
The Wedding Planner	PG-13	language and some sexual humor	80	2001	NA	82
Blow	R	"pervasive drug content and language, some violence and sexuality"	100	2001	78	80
High School Musical	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	64	80
High School Musical 2	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2007	58	80
Twilight	PG-13	some violence and one sexual scene	80	2008	89	80
Hannah Montana: The Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	56	80
The Office (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	97	80
Bones	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	97	80
Law & Order: Special Victims Unit	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	97	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
Nurse Jackie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	82	80
NCIS	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	97	80
Gossip Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	96	80
How I Met Your Mother	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	94	80
Supernatural	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Parks and Recreation	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	94	80
Glee	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	92	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
Criminal Minds	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Friends	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2003	98	80
Mean Girls 2	PG-13	"For some rude and suggestive material, and for language."	80	2011	NA	82
The Secret Life of the American Teenager	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	81	80
One Tree Hill	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	90	80
Army Wives	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	61	80
Gilmore Girls	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2006	91	80
Private Practice	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	88	80
Parenthood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	79	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Revenge	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	84	80
Scandal	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	92	80
Magic Mike	R	"pervasive sexual content, brief graphic nudity, language and some drug use"	100	2012	77	80
Trouble with the Curve	PG-13	Parents strongly cautioned. May be inappropriate for children under 13.	80	2012	63	80
Orange Is the New Black	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	98	80
Baby Daddy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	80	80
The Night Shift	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	93	80
The Originals	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
Home	PG	mild action and some rude humor	60	2015	94	80
How to Get Away with Murder	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Zootopia	PG	"some thematic elements, rude humor and action"	60	2016	97	80
Finding Dory	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2016	98	80
Sausage Party	R	"strong crude sexual content, pervasive language, and drug use"	100	2016	91	80
Skin Wars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	69	80
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
Felipe Neto: My Life Makes No Sense	TV-MA		110	2017	NA	82
Cheer Squad	TV-PG		70	2016	61	80
Lost	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2010	98	80
Weeds	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2012	85	80
The Tudors	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2010	NA	82
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Lie to Me	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2010	89	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
Gossip Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	96	80
Glee	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	92	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
The Secret Life of the American Teenager	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	81	80
Drop Dead Diva	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	NA	82
Gilmore Girls	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2006	91	80
Charmed	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2005	90	80
White Collar	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	93	80
House of Cards	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	91	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
The Killing	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	73	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
Hart of Dixie	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	81	80
Once Upon a Time	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	98	80
Scandal	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	92	80
The Client List	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	92	80
Unconditional	PG-13	some violent content and mature thematic elements	80	2012	NA	82
Bates Motel	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	83	80
The Blacklist	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
The Fosters	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	73	80
Reign	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	79	80
The Originals	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	74	80
The 100	NR	This movie has not been rated.	124	2016	97	80
Witches of East End	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	NA	82
Bitten	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	56	80
London Has Fallen	R	strong violence and language throughout	100	2016	96	80
Marvel's Jessica Jones	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	83	80
Bloodline	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Grace and Frankie	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	90	80
Velvet	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
How to Get Away with Murder	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
The Crown	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	84	80
Jane The Virgin	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Kurt Seyit & Sura	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	NA	82
The Returned	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	NA	82
The Girl in the Book	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	NA	82
Quantico	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	88	80
Life in Pieces	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	68	80
Ingobernable	TV-MA		110	2017	96	80
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
MerlÌ?	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	NA	82
Greenleaf	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	62	80
100 Metros	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
Bones	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	97	80
Dexter	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	95	80
Leverage	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	86	80
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Lie to Me	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2010	89	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
NCIS	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	97	80
Burn Notice	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	85	80
Breaking Bad	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2013	97	80
Criminal Minds	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
White Collar	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	93	80
Luther	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	69	80
Hawaii Five-0	TV-14	"dialogue, language, sexual situations and violence"	90	2016	96	80
House of Cards	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	91	80
Last Man Standing	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	97	80
Revenge	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	84	80
Person of Interest	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	93	80
Scandal	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	92	80
Touch	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	68	80
Sherlock	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Breakout Kings	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	88	80
The Client List	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	92	80
Arrow	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	96	80
The Following	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	NA	82
"Drugs, Inc."	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	NA	82
Longmire	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	92	80
Ripper Street	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
The Fall	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	61	80
Death in Paradise	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	77	80
Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	89	80
Crossing Lines	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	66	80
London Has Fallen	R	strong violence and language throughout	100	2016	96	80
Halt and Catch Fire	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Marvel's Iron Fist	TV-MA		110	2017	98	80
The Honorable Woman	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2014	NA	82
Transporter: The Series	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2014	NA	82
Gotham	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	85	80
Better Call Saul	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	95	80
How to Get Away with Murder	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
Narcos	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	94	80
American Odyssey	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	NA	82
Aquarius	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2015	NA	82
Hap and Leonard	TV-MA		110	2016	57	80
Rosewood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	81	80
Quantico	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	88	80
Limitless	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	84	80
Travelers	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	86	80
The Doctor Blake Mysteries	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	57	80
I.T	NR		124	2016	NA	82
Bordertown	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	NA	82
The Office (U.S.)	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	97	80
Grey's Anatomy	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Law & Order: Special Victims Unit	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	97	80
Lie to Me	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2010	89	80
Prison Break	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2008	98	80
90210	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	62	80
Gossip Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2012	96	80
How I Met Your Mother	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	94	80
Parks and Recreation	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	94	80
The Vampire Diaries	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2017	91	80
Criminal Minds	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	98	80
Friends	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2003	98	80
The West Wing	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2005	79	80
Parenthood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	79	80
White Collar	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	93	80
Blue Bloods	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
House of Cards	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	91	80
Pretty Little Liars	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
The Killing	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2014	73	80
Shameless (U.S.)	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	97	80
New Girl	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	91	80
Revenge	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2015	84	80
Person of Interest	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	93	80
Once Upon a Time	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	98	80
Scandal	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	92	80
Forensic Files	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2011	88	80
Sherlock	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	95	80
The Client List	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2013	92	80
Orange Is the New Black	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	98	80
Rectify	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Black Mirror	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	80	80
Bates Motel	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	83	80
The Fall	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	61	80
The Blacklist	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	96	80
Being Mary Jane: The Series	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
American Crime	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Madam Secretary	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	70	80
Sense8	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	81	80
Scream	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Rosewood	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2015	81	80
The Great British Baking Show	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2016	94	80
Quantico	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	88	80
Limitless	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	84	80
American Crime Story: The People v. O.J. Simpson	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	79	80
Santa Clarita Diet	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	82	80
No Tomorrow	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	NA	82
Girlboss	TV-MA		110	2017	94	80
13 Reasons Why	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2017	99	80
The Doctor Blake Mysteries	TV-MA	For mature audiences.  May not be suitable for children 17 and under.	110	2016	57	80
Greenleaf	TV-14	Parents strongly cautioned. May be unsuitable for children ages 14 and under.	90	2016	62	80
The Nightmare Before Christmas	PG	some scary images	60	1993	84	80
Scooby-Doo	PG	"some rude humor, language and some scary action"	60	2002	86	80
Chicken Little	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	92	80
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles	PG	"animated action violence, some scary cartoon images and mild language"	60	2007	NA	82
Star Wars: The Clone Wars	PG	"sci-fi action violence throughout, brief language and momentary smoking"	60	2008	57	80
Coraline	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, some language and suggestive humor"	60	2009	95	80
The Smurfs and the Magic Flute	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1976	NA	82
We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	NA	82
Thomas & Friends: Thomas & the Runaway Kite	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2010	NA	82
Dino Squad	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2008	NA	82
Cars Toons: Mater's Tall Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	74	80
LeapFrog: The Amazing Alphabet Amusement Park	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2010	NA	82
Star Wars: The Clone Wars	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2014	93	80
Phineas and Ferb	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	89	80
The Batman	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2007	77	80
Justice League	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2003	66	80
Justice League Unlimited	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2005	NA	82
Mighty Morphin Power Rangers	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2010	73	80
Young Justice	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	71	80
The Super Mario Bros. Super Show!	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1989	NA	82
Power Rangers Zeo	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	1996	NA	82
Oscar's Oasis	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2011	NA	82
Transformers Prime	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2013	NA	82
The Adventures of Chuck & Friends	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2011	NA	82
Transformers: Rescue Bots	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
Thomas & Friends: King of the Railway	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
LEGO: Marvel Super Heroes: Maximum Overload	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2013	NA	82
Max Steel	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2014	NA	82
Transformers Prime Beast Hunters: Predacons Rising	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2013	NA	82
Agent F.O.X.	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2014	NA	82
VeggieTales in the House	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Thunder and the House Of Magic	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
All Hail King Julien	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	71	80
Kong: King of the Apes	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	NA	82
Marvel Super Hero Adventures: Frost Fight!	PG	fantasy action	60	2015	NA	82
Slugterra: Slug Fu Showdown	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2015	NA	82
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Edgar Rice Burroughs' Tarzan and Jane	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Lego DC Comics: Batman Be-Leaguered	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2014	NA	82
Trollhunters	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	83	80
Power Rangers Dino Charge	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2015	NA	82
Bunks	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2013	NA	82
The Jungle Book	PG	for some sequences of scary action and peril	60	2016	97	80
The Angry Birds Movie	PG	for rude humor and action	60	2016	92	80
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
The Furchester Hotel	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Marvel's Hulk: Where Monsters Dwell	PG	"action violence throughout, some scary images, and language"	60	2016	NA	82
Angry Birds	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
Talking Tom and Friends	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	61	80
Nexo Knights	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2015	NA	82
The Nightmare Before Christmas	PG	some scary images	60	1993	84	80
An Extremely Goofy Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	67	80
Scooby-Doo	PG	"some rude humor, language and some scary action"	60	2002	86	80
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
Star Wars: The Clone Wars	PG	"sci-fi action violence throughout, brief language and momentary smoking"	60	2008	57	80
Cars Toons: Mater's Tall Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	74	80
The Batman	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2007	77	80
Justice League	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2003	66	80
Justice League Unlimited	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2005	NA	82
The Cat in the Hat Knows a Lot About That!	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2014	NA	82
Mighty Morphin Power Rangers	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2010	73	80
Bob the Builder	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Beyblade: Metal Fusion	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2009	NA	82
Ninja Turtles: The Next Mutation	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	1997	NA	82
Transformers Prime	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2013	NA	82
DreamWorks Kung Fu Panda Awesome Secrets	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2008	NA	82
LEGO Ninjago: Masters of Spinjitzu	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2015	67	80
Transformers: Rescue Bots	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
Goosebumps	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1998	88	80
LEGO Ninjago: Masters of Spinjitzu: Way of the Ninja	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2011	NA	82
Super Buddies	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
Tad: The Lost Explorer	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	NA	82
PokÌ©mon: Indigo League	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2000	74	80
Ratchet and Clank	PG	action and some rude humor	60	2016	74	80
Pac-Man and the Ghostly Adventures	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2014	NA	82
Iron Man & Captain America: Heroes United	PG	"action and violence throughout, and mild language"	60	2014	NA	82
Power Rangers Super Megaforce	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2014	NA	82
Chuggington	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
All Hail King Julien	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	71	80
The Adventures of Puss in Boots	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	78	80
Kong: King of the Apes	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	NA	82
Marvel Super Hero Adventures: Frost Fight!	PG	fantasy action	60	2015	NA	82
Some Assembly Required	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	NA	82
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Edgar Rice Burroughs' Tarzan and Jane	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Kulipari: An Army of Frogs	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	NA	82
Transformers: Robots in Disguise	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
Robocar Poli	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2012	NA	82
LEGO Bionicle: The Journey to One	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	NA	82
Lego DC Comics: Batman Be-Leaguered	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2014	NA	82
Voltron: Legendary Defender	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Trollhunters	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	83	80
Buddy Thunderstruck	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2017	NA	82
Power Rangers Dino Charge	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2015	NA	82
PokÌ©mon: XY	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2015	56	80
Power Rangers Dino Super Charge	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
The Deep	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2015	NA	82
Skylanders Academy	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
Marvel's Hulk: Where Monsters Dwell	PG	"action violence throughout, some scary images, and language"	60	2016	NA	82
Growing Up Wild	G		35	2016	80	80
The Little Rascals	PG	some rude dialogue	60	1994	86	80
Flubber	PG	slapstick action and mild language	60	1997	83	80
Tarzan	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	95	80
The Emperor's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	95	80
Scooby-Doo	PG	"some rude humor, language and some scary action"	60	2002	86	80
Lilo & Stitch	PG	mild sci-fi action	60	2002	95	80
Scooby-Doo 2: Monsters Unleashed	PG	"some scary action, rude humor and language"	60	2004	82	80
The Three Musketeers	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2004	NA	82
Mickey's Twice Upon a Christmas	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2004	NA	82
The Pacifier	PG	"action violence, language and rude humor"	60	2005	91	80
Chicken Little	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	92	80
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles	PG	"animated action violence, some scary cartoon images and mild language"	60	2007	NA	82
Bee Movie	PG	mild suggestive humor	60	2007	94	80
Kung Fu Panda	PG	sequences of martial arts action	60	2008	91	80
Coraline	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, some language and suggestive humor"	60	2009	95	80
Cars Toons: Mater's Tall Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	74	80
Phineas and Ferb	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	89	80
Super Why!	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	68	80
Jessie	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	88	80
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 1: Mickey and the Beanstalk	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
Lab Rats	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	85	80
Masha and the Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	81	80
Pocoyo	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	67	80
Home	PG	mild action and some rude humor	60	2015	94	80
Chuggington	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Octonauts	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Dragons: Race to the Edge	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	88	80
Mother Goose Club	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Little Einsteins	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	70	80
Hotel Transylvania 2	PG	"some scary images, action and rude humor"	60	2015	93	80
Dawn of the Croods	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2017	72	80
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Goosebumps	PG	"scary and intense creature action and images, and for some rude humor"	60	2015	90	80
Kung Fu Panda 3	PG	martial arts action and some mild rude humor	60	2016	92	80
Zootopia	PG	"some thematic elements, rude humor and action"	60	2016	97	80
The Jungle Book	PG	for some sequences of scary action and peril	60	2016	97	80
Home: Adventures with Tip & Oh	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2017	NA	82
Open Season: Scared Silly	PG	rude humor and some action	60	2015	72	80
The Land Before Time XIV: Journey of the Brave	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
The Angry Birds Movie	PG	for rude humor and action	60	2016	92	80
Alice Through the Looking Glass	PG	fantasy action/peril and some language	60	2016	96	80
Finding Dory	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2016	98	80
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
Ask the StoryBots	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
The Furchester Hotel	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Goldie & Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	77	80
Little Baby Bum: Nursery Rhyme Friends	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Angry Birds	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
Tayo the Little Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2014	NA	82
Talking Tom and Friends	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	61	80
The Little Rascals	PG	some rude dialogue	60	1994	86	80
Antz	PG	moderate adult language and intense action	60	1998	80	80
Tarzan	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	95	80
An Extremely Goofy Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	67	80
Chicken Run	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	80	80
The Emperor's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	95	80
Lilo & Stitch	PG	mild sci-fi action	60	2002	95	80
Spy Kids 3: Game Over	PG	action sequences and peril	60	2003	64	80
Annie	PG	adult content and mld violence	60	1982	68	80
Mulan 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2004	85	80
Chicken Little	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	92	80
Lilo & Stitch 2: Stitch Has A Glitch	PG	some mild action	60	2005	85	80
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles	PG	"animated action violence, some scary cartoon images and mild language"	60	2007	NA	82
Bee Movie	PG	mild suggestive humor	60	2007	94	80
Kung Fu Panda	PG	sequences of martial arts action	60	2008	91	80
Cars Toons: Mater's Tall Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	74	80
Super Why!	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	68	80
DreamWorks Shrek's Swamp Stories	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2008	56	80
Beverly Hills Chihuahua 3: Viva La Fiesta!	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	NA	82
DreamWorks Spooky Stories: Volume 2	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2011	NA	82
The Magic School Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1997	81	80
Goosebumps	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1998	88	80
Sammy 2	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	NA	82
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 1: Mickey and the Beanstalk	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
Masha and the Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	81	80
Pocoyo	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	67	80
Sofia the First	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	82	80
Barbie Life in the Dreamhouse	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	85	80
Paddington	PG	mild action and rude humor	60	2014	70	80
Larva	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	NA	82
Sid the Science Kid	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2008	NA	82
Chuggington	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
All Hail King Julien	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	71	80
Octonauts	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Minions	PG	action and rude humor	60	2015	96	80
Dragons: Race to the Edge	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	88	80
Little Einsteins	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	70	80
Hotel Transylvania 2	PG	"some scary images, action and rude humor"	60	2015	93	80
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
The Little Prince	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2015	71	80
Word Party	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Zootopia	PG	"some thematic elements, rude humor and action"	60	2016	97	80
The Jungle Book	PG	for some sequences of scary action and peril	60	2016	97	80
Home: Adventures with Tip & Oh	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2017	NA	82
Open Season: Scared Silly	PG	rude humor and some action	60	2015	72	80
The Angry Birds Movie	PG	for rude humor and action	60	2016	92	80
Finding Dory	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2016	98	80
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
Goldie & Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	77	80
Talking Tom and Friends	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	61	80
Cool Runnings	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1993	81	80
Homeward Bound: The Incredible Journey	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	96	80
The Little Rascals	PG	some rude dialogue	60	1994	86	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
Tarzan	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	95	80
The Emperor's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	95	80
Scooby-Doo	PG	"some rude humor, language and some scary action"	60	2002	86	80
Lilo & Stitch	PG	mild sci-fi action	60	2002	95	80
Missione Hamburger	PG	"language, some comic violence and mild sex-related humor"	60	1997	75	80
Chicken Little	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	92	80
Curious George	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	55	80
Bee Movie	PG	mild suggestive humor	60	2007	94	80
Kung Fu Panda	PG	sequences of martial arts action	60	2008	91	80
Coraline	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, some language and suggestive humor"	60	2009	95	80
Cars Toons: Mater's Tall Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2010	74	80
Super Why!	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	68	80
Jessie	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	88	80
Secret of the Wings	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	65	80
The Magic School Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1997	81	80
Sammy 2	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	NA	82
Masha and the Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	81	80
Sofia the First	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	82	80
Barbie Life in the Dreamhouse	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	85	80
Clifford the Big Red Dog	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2002	NA	82
Home	PG	mild action and some rude humor	60	2015	94	80
Paddington	PG	mild action and rude humor	60	2014	70	80
Chuggington	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Octonauts	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Minions	PG	action and rude humor	60	2015	96	80
Dragons: Race to the Edge	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	88	80
Little Einsteins	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	70	80
Hotel Transylvania 2	PG	"some scary images, action and rude humor"	60	2015	93	80
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
Walt Disney Animation Studios Short Films Collection	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	84	80
Kung Fu Panda 3	PG	martial arts action and some mild rude humor	60	2016	92	80
Bunk'd	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	61	80
Zootopia	PG	"some thematic elements, rude humor and action"	60	2016	97	80
The Jungle Book	PG	for some sequences of scary action and peril	60	2016	97	80
Open Season: Scared Silly	PG	rude humor and some action	60	2015	72	80
The Land Before Time XIV: Journey of the Brave	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
The Angry Birds Movie	PG	for rude humor and action	60	2016	92	80
Alice Through the Looking Glass	PG	fantasy action/peril and some language	60	2016	96	80
The BFG	PG	"for action/peril, some scary moments and brief rude humor"	60	2016	97	80
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
Pete's Dragon	PG	"for action, peril and brief language"	60	2016	93	80
Kubo and the Two Strings	PG	"thematic elements, scary images, action and peril"	60	2016	96	80
Goldie & Bear	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	77	80
Little Baby Bum: Nursery Rhyme Friends	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Growing Up Wild	G		35	2016	80	80
The Real Ghostbusters	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1990	65	80
Cool Runnings	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1993	81	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
Antz	PG	moderate adult language and intense action	60	1998	80	80
Babe: Pig in the City	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Prince of Egypt	PG	intense scenes dealing with strong content	60	1998	81	80
Paulie	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1998	NA	82
Tarzan	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	95	80
The Road to El Dorado	PG	mild thematic material and language	60	2000	91	80
Fantasia 2000	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	NA	82
Pocahontas II: Journey to a New World	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	64	80
The Emperor's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	95	80
Fantasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1940	61	80
An American Tail	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1986	67	80
Pooh's Grand Adventure: The Search for Christopher Robin	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
FernGully 2: The Magical Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
Balto 2: Wolf Quest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2001	NA	82
Balto	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1995	64	80
Back to the Secret Garden	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2002	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster to the Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
An American Tail: The Mystery of the Night Monster	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	NA	82
An American Tail: Fievel Goes West	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1991	NA	82
The Last Unicorn	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1982	NA	82
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
Brother Bear 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	57	80
The Fox and the Hound 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	NA	82
The Smurfs and the Magic Flute	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1976	NA	82
Jetsons: The Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1990	NA	82
We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	NA	82
A Monster in Paris	PG	"some action violence involving gunplay, and mild rude humor"	60	2011	NA	82
The Gruffalo	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2009	NA	82
DreamWorks How to Train Your Dragon Legends	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2011	NA	82
Ernest & Celestine	PG	some scary moments	60	2012	NA	82
The Magic School Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1997	81	80
Animaniacs	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1997	72	80
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 4: The Tortoise and the Hare	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
PopPixie	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2011	NA	82
Jack and the Cuckoo-Clock Heart	PG	"scary images, suggestive material, some language and smoking"	60	2013	NA	82
The Pirate Fairy	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	57	80
Axel: The Biggest Little Hero	PG	"some scary images, perilous action sequences and mild rude humor"	60	2013	NA	82
The Adventures of Figaro Pho	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2015	NA	82
The Boxcar Children	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Pet Pals in Windland	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Walt Disney Animation Studios Short Films Collection	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	84	80
Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
Alice Through the Looking Glass	PG	fantasy action/peril and some language	60	2016	96	80
Quackerz	PG	"rude and suggestive humor, and some action"	60	2016	NA	82
Hatched	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2013	NA	82
Blinky Bill: The Movie	PG	some rude humor	60	2015	NA	82
The Real Ghostbusters	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1990	65	80
Flubber	PG	slapstick action and mild language	60	1997	83	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
An Extremely Goofy Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	67	80
An American Tail	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1986	67	80
Scooby-Doo	PG	"some rude humor, language and some scary action"	60	2002	86	80
FernGully: The Last Rainforest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1992	70	80
Balto 2: Wolf Quest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2001	NA	82
Balto	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1995	64	80
The Lizzie McGuire Movie	PG	mild thematic elements	60	2003	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster to the Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
Recess: Taking the Fifth Grade	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	NA	82
An American Tail: The Mystery of the Night Monster	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	NA	82
An American Tail: Fievel Goes West	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1991	NA	82
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
The Very Hungry Caterpillar and Other Stories	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1993	NA	82
The Hero of Color City	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Dino Squad	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2008	NA	82
The Little Engine That Could	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2011	NA	82
Delhi Safari	PG	"violence and menacing action, rude humor, suggestive content and thematic elements"	60	2012	NA	82
Ninja Turtles: The Next Mutation	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	1997	NA	82
Pound Puppies	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	NA	82
Sammy 2	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2012	NA	82
Monster Math Squad	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	NA	82
Care Bears: Welcome to Care-a-Lot	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2012	NA	82
Clifford the Big Red Dog	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2002	NA	82
Clifford's Puppy Days	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2003	NA	82
Axel: The Biggest Little Hero	PG	"some scary images, perilous action sequences and mild rude humor"	60	2013	NA	82
Agent F.O.X.	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2014	NA	82
Dinosaur King	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2008	NA	82
Ribbit	PG	some peril	60	2014	NA	82
Chuggington	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Rooster Doodle-doo	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Octonauts	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Kong: King of the Apes	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2016	NA	82
My Animal Friends	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	NA	82
Worms	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2013	NA	82
Puffin Rock	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2016	NA	82
Little Einsteins	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2007	70	80
Hotel Transylvania 2	PG	"some scary images, action and rude humor"	60	2015	93	80
Dinotrux	TV-Y7-FV	Suitable for children ages 7 and older.  Content contains fantasy violence.	42	2017	NA	82
The Mr. Peabody and Sherman Show	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2017	NA	82
Zoobabu	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2010	NA	82
Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
Gon	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
Sid the Science Kid: The Movie	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2012	NA	82
The Land Before Time XIV: Journey of the Brave	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
LEGO Jurassic World: The Indominus Escape	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2016	NA	82
The Real Ghostbusters	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1990	65	80
Cool Runnings	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1993	81	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
Antz	PG	moderate adult language and intense action	60	1998	80	80
Babe: Pig in the City	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Prince of Egypt	PG	intense scenes dealing with strong content	60	1998	81	80
Paulie	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1998	NA	82
Tarzan	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	95	80
The Road to El Dorado	PG	mild thematic material and language	60	2000	91	80
Fantasia 2000	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	NA	82
Pocahontas II: Journey to a New World	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	64	80
The Emperor's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	95	80
Fantasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1940	61	80
An American Tail	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1986	67	80
Pooh's Grand Adventure: The Search for Christopher Robin	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
FernGully 2: The Magical Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
Balto 2: Wolf Quest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2001	NA	82
Balto	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1995	64	80
Back to the Secret Garden	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2002	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster to the Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
An American Tail: The Mystery of the Night Monster	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	NA	82
An American Tail: Fievel Goes West	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1991	NA	82
The Last Unicorn	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1982	NA	82
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
Brother Bear 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	57	80
The Fox and the Hound 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	NA	82
The Smurfs and the Magic Flute	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1976	NA	82
Jetsons: The Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1990	NA	82
We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	NA	82
A Monster in Paris	PG	"some action violence involving gunplay, and mild rude humor"	60	2011	NA	82
The Gruffalo	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2009	NA	82
DreamWorks How to Train Your Dragon Legends	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2011	NA	82
Ernest & Celestine	PG	some scary moments	60	2012	NA	82
The Magic School Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1997	81	80
Animaniacs	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1997	72	80
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 4: The Tortoise and the Hare	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
PopPixie	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2011	NA	82
Jack and the Cuckoo-Clock Heart	PG	"scary images, suggestive material, some language and smoking"	60	2013	NA	82
The Pirate Fairy	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	57	80
Axel: The Biggest Little Hero	PG	"some scary images, perilous action sequences and mild rude humor"	60	2013	NA	82
The Adventures of Figaro Pho	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2015	NA	82
The Boxcar Children	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Pet Pals in Windland	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Walt Disney Animation Studios Short Films Collection	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	84	80
Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
Alice Through the Looking Glass	PG	fantasy action/peril and some language	60	2016	96	80
Quackerz	PG	"rude and suggestive humor, and some action"	60	2016	NA	82
Hatched	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2013	NA	82
Blinky Bill: The Movie	PG	some rude humor	60	2015	NA	82
The Real Ghostbusters	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1990	65	80
Cool Runnings	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1993	81	80
Homeward Bound: The Incredible Journey	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	96	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
Antz	PG	moderate adult language and intense action	60	1998	80	80
Babe: Pig in the City	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Road to El Dorado	PG	mild thematic material and language	60	2000	91	80
Fantasia 2000	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	NA	82
Fantasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1940	61	80
Harry and the Hendersons	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1987	58	80
Pooh's Grand Adventure: The Search for Christopher Robin	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
Cats & Dogs	PG	animal action and humor	60	2001	NA	82
Atlantis: The Lost Empire	PG	action violence	60	2001	96	80
FernGully: The Last Rainforest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1992	70	80
Balto 2: Wolf Quest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2001	NA	82
Balto	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1995	64	80
Back to the Secret Garden	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2002	NA	82
Tarzan & Jane	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2002	NA	82
Atlantis: Milo's Return	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	79	80
The Brave Little Toaster Goes to Mars	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
The Brave Little Toaster to the Rescue	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	NA	82
Annie	PG	adult content and mld violence	60	1982	68	80
Recess: Taking the Fifth Grade	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	NA	82
An American Tail: The Mystery of the Night Monster	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1999	NA	82
Batched	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	NA	82
An American Tail: Fievel Goes West	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1991	NA	82
Winnie the Pooh: Springtime with Roo	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2004	NA	82
The Last Unicorn	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1982	NA	82
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
Mulan 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2004	85	80
Pooh's Heffalump Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	NA	82
Kronk's New Groove	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2005	NA	82
Corpse Bride	PG	"some scary images and action, and brief mild language"	60	2005	91	80
Brother Bear 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	57	80
The Smurfs and the Magic Flute	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1976	NA	82
Jetsons: The Movie	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1990	NA	82
We're Back! A Dinosaur's Story	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1993	NA	82
Ernest & Celestine	PG	some scary moments	60	2012	NA	82
Animaniacs	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	1997	72	80
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 1: Mickey and the Beanstalk	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 2: Three Little Pigs	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
Disney Animation Collection: Vol. 4: The Tortoise and the Hare	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2009	NA	82
The Pirate Fairy	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	57	80
Underdogs	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2013	NA	82
The Boxcar Children	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2014	NA	82
Ribbit	PG	some peril	60	2014	NA	82
Yellowbird	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	2014	NA	82
Octonauts	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
The Land Before Time XIV: Journey of the Brave	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
Quackerz	PG	"rude and suggestive humor, and some action"	60	2016	NA	82
Growing Up Wild	G		35	2016	80	80
Cool Runnings	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1993	81	80
Mr. Magoo	PG	mild language and action sequences	60	1997	NA	82
Flubber	PG	slapstick action and mild language	60	1997	83	80
Anastasia	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1997	93	80
Antz	PG	moderate adult language and intense action	60	1998	80	80
Babe: Pig in the City	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1998	NA	82
Paulie	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1998	NA	82
The Road to El Dorado	PG	mild thematic material and language	60	2000	91	80
Air Bud: World Pup	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2000	NA	82
An American Tail	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1986	67	80
Harry and the Hendersons	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1987	58	80
Cats & Dogs	PG	animal action and humor	60	2001	NA	82
Baby's Day Out	PG	mild language and comic action	60	1994	71	80
Balto 2: Wolf Quest	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2001	NA	82
Balto	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1995	64	80
Back to the Secret Garden	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2002	NA	82
Blank Check	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1994	93	80
Heavyweights	PG	some rude language and pranks	60	1995	74	80
Inspector Gadget 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	NA	82
Air Bud: Spikes Back	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	NA	82
Annie	PG	adult content and mld violence	60	1982	68	80
An American Tail: Fievel Goes West	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	1991	NA	82
D2: The Mighty Ducks	PG	some mild language and rough hockey action	60	1994	70	80
"Honey, I Shrunk the Kids"	PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for children.	60	1989	80	80
The Iron Giant	PG	fantasy action and mild language	60	1999	83	80
The Fox and the Hound 2	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2006	NA	82
Air Buddies	PG	"some mild, rude humor"	60	2006	NA	82
Dr. Dolittle: Tail to the Chief	PG	brief mild language and some rude behavior	60	2008	NA	82
Flicka 2	PG	some reckless behavior	60	2010	NA	82
H2O: Just Add Water	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2009	74	80
The Gruffalo	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2009	NA	82
Dolphin Tale	PG	some mild thematic elements	60	2011	NA	82
Pound Puppies	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	NA	82
Beverly Hills Chihuahua 3: Viva La Fiesta!	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2012	NA	82
The Magic School Bus	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	1997	81	80
Step Dogs	TV-PG	Parental guidance suggested. May not be suitable for all children.	70	2013	NA	82
PokÌ©mon: Indigo League	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2000	74	80
Mia and Me	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2015	NA	82
Paddington	PG	mild action and rude humor	60	2014	70	80
Russell Madness	PG	some rude humor and sports action	60	2015	NA	82
My Animal Friends	TV-Y	Suitable for all ages.	10	2013	NA	82
Dawn of the Croods	TV-Y7	Suitable for children ages 7 and older	41	2017	72	80
Alpha and Omega: Dino Digs	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
Wiener Dog Internationals	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2015	NA	82
Pup Star	G	General Audiences. Suitable for all ages.	35	2016	NA	82
The BFG	PG	"for action/peril, some scary moments and brief rude humor"	60	2016	97	80
The Secret Life of Pets	PG	for action and some rude humor	60	2016	NA	81
Precious Puppies	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2003	NA	82
Beary Tales	TV-G	Suitable for all ages.	35	2013	NA	82
Growing Up Wild	G		35	2016	80	80
